Guide to the Morris Schappes Papers TAM.179
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Audio-Visual Material, 1953-2000
  - Subseries VE: Reel-to-Reel Tapes Addendum
    - Plenary Session: Welcome, Lecture, Taxation Banquet, undated (Box 44, Reel 121)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1920-2002
  - Images for Morris Schappes Induction into the Townsend Harris Alumni Association Hall of Fame, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Eightieth Birthday Celebration, May 17, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Events Related to Rapp-Coudert Investigation and Schappes Trial, circa 1940-1942 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Events and Speaking Engagement (includes images from 90th and 95th birthday celebrations), 1982-2002; NPA.2005.243 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Currents, 1966, 1976, 1980-1990, undated; NPA.2005.243 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Currents (includes photos from events and images for publication), 1966, 1980-1996, undated; NPA.2006.021 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
  - Jewish Currents - 1998 Israel Celebration, NPA.2005.243 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Currents Events (portraits of participants), 1987, 1993, 2000-2002; 2009.086 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Personal Photographs (includes photos of friends and family and Schappes teaching at CCNY), 1920-1989, undated (Box 45, Folder 10-11)
  - Portrait- Ernestine Rose, undated; 2009.086 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Portraits - Morris Schappes, circa 1940, 1950,1995, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Schappes at New York College Teachers Local 537, AFT Rally, undated; NPA.2006.021 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Image (possibly Alice P. Barrows), undated (Box 45, Folder 15)